outdoorsy.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Outdoorsy

### Last Updated: February 16, 2015

Outdoorsy, Inc., Operating as Outdoorsy, (“ **Outdoorsy** “, “ **we** ” or “ **us** “) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of [https://www.outdoorsy.co](https://www.outdoorsy.com/) (collectively, the “ **Site** “) and any other products or services made available by Outdoorsy, all of the foregoing are, collectively, the “ **Services** ”. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Services. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to  
the e-mail address specified in your Outdoorsy Account) or by means of a notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use (<https://www.outdoorsy.com/help/outdoorsy-terms-and-conditions-and-conditions>.  
As used in this policy, the terms “ **using** ” and “ **processing** ” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

### International Transfer

YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO – AND MAINTAINED ON – COMPUTERS LOCATED OUTSIDE OF YOUR STATE, PROVINCE, COUNTRY OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL JURISDICTION WHERE THE PRIVACY LAWS MAY NOT BE AS PROTECTIVE AS THOSE IN YOUR JURISDICTION. IF YOU ARE LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES AND CHOOSE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION TO US, OUTDOORSY TRANSFERS PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND PROCESSES IT THERE. YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOLLOWED BY YOUR SUBMISSION OF SUCH INFORMATION REPRESENTS YOUR AGREEMENT TO THAT TRANSFER.

### Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, Services, features and content, to administer your use of the Site and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

### Personally Identifiable Information

When you register with us through the Services and become a Member, when you choose to post a Listing or rent a Vehicle, or when you wish to contact another Member, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“ **Identity Information** “). Identity Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, drivers license, email address, social security number (SSN), and home postal address, but does not include your credit card number or billing information. In order to process some of your transactions through the Services, we may also ask for your credit card number and other billing information (“ **Billing Information** “) (Identity Information and Billing Information together, “ **Personal Information** “). Some Personal Information is required, like your name and email address, and other Personal Information is optional, like your date of birth. We use your Personal Information to provide the Service and administer your inquiries.  
We collect Personal Information in connection with your registration to join the Service. You can register to join via the Site or Application by completing the required forms.  
You can also register to join by logging into online accounts you may have with third party service providers (“ **TPA** “) (e.g. Facebook); each such account, a “ **Third Party Account** “, via our Site or Application as described below. As part of the functionality of the Site, Service and Application, you may link your Outdoorsy Account with Third Party Accounts, by either: (i) providing your Third Party Account login information to Outdoorsy through the Site, Service or Application; or (ii) allowing Outdoorsy to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to Outdoorsy and/or grant Outdoorsy access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for use for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating Outdoorsy to pay any fees or making Outdoorsy subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable TPA. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via our Site or Application, we will obtain the Personal Information you have provided to the applicable TPA (such as your  
“ **real** ” name, email address, profile picture, names of TPA friends, names of TPA groups to which you belong, other information you make publicly available via the applicable TPA and/or other information you authorize Outdoorsy to access  
by authorizing the TPA to provide such information) from your Third Party Accounts and use that information to create your Outdoorsy Account and Outdoorsy Account profile page and you will become a Member. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we will access, make available and store (if applicable and as permitted by the TPA and authorized by you) the information in your Third Party Accounts so that it is available on and through your Outdoorsy Account on the Site, Service and Application. If there is information about your “ **friends** ” or people with whom you are associated in your Third Party Account, the information we obtain about those “ **friends** ” or people with  
whom you are associated, may also depend on the privacy settings such people  
have with the applicable TPA.  
We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your Outdoorsy Account profile (e.g., without limitation, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences or demographic information) (“ **Non-Identifying Information** “).  
We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non- Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries.  
Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be  
identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non- identifying information (for example, your demographic information). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Outdoorsy Users (defined below) to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how our Services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.  
We also use your Personal Information to contact you with Outdoorsy newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “ **Notifications** ” information. (See “ **Changing or Deleting Information** ,” below.) We may also share the combined information without aggregating it to partners we feel may have material benefit to you or your use of the Site. Please note that we may  
also use your Personal Information to contact you with information related to your use of the Service, or services from Partners; you may not opt out of these notifications.

### Log Data

When you visit the Services, whether as a Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “ **Outdoorsy User** “), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“ **Log Data** “). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“ **IP** “) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Services, pages or features of our Services that you visit or use, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Services,  
access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor  
and analyze use of the Services and for the technical administration of the Services, to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of the Services, and to better tailor our Services to our visitors’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Services meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze  
and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.

### Cookies

Like many websites, we use “ **cookies** ” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Services. Second, we  
utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor aggregate usage by Outdoorsy Users and web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Services and then close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Services may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions or functionality of the Service.

### Web Beacons

Our Services may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our Services are used and may be used in  
some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

### Emailing Via a Outdoorsy Account

As part of the Service, Outdoorsy Users may communicate with Outdoorsy Members through use of the “ **Contact Owner** ” feature on the Services. If the functionality exists for Outdoorsy Users to have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template will be sent from Outdoorsy to those email addresses on their behalf.

### Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “ **phishing** ” are of great concern to Outdoorsy. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your Outdoorsy Account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Overview

The Services can be used to facilitate the listing and booking of Vehicles. Listings for such Vehicles are made available via the Services by Owners. Listings posted by Owners, ratings and reviews of Owners and Renters, and the Profile Information (as defined below) of Owners and Renters, are visible to any Outdoorsy User.

### Outdoorsy Members and Users

When you create an Outdoorsy Account, we will set up an Outdoorsy Account profile page for you. Your Outdoorsy Account profile page will include your first name and last initial and connections you have established between your Account and any TPAs, and a biography and links to your Listings. You can select the other items of Personal Information that you wish to be included in your Outdoorsy Account profile page – including, but not limited to, a profile picture, or, other information knows as your “ **Profile Information** “. We will display your Profile Information in your Outdoorsy Account profile page publicly via the Services, and, with your prior permission, on third party sites. Any information you choose to provide as part of your Profile Information will be  
publicly visible to all Outdoorsy Users and consequently should reflect how much you want other Outdoorsy Users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage members to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your Profile Information at any time.

### Listings

If you publish a listing, your Outdoorsy listing, and any personally identifiable information associated with your public listing, may be shared with and distributed by external 3rd parties. Such 3rd parties may include, but are not limited to, external marketplaces, local and national classifieds, and any other approved Outdoorsy partners. We may also display the geographical location of your Listing in the form of a map or an obscured address to potential Renters as well as any listing data or media shared by you.

Outdoorsy is not responsible for any information included in your listings, and cannot be held liable should it be distributed without your explicit consent or permission. Should an Outdoorsy customer feel their listing data shouldn’t be shared and would not like bookings from third party sources it is the customer’s responsibility to contact Outdoorsy at fboptout@outdoorsy.com and request that said listing data is removed.

If you request to make a booking via the Services, Outdoorsy will share the following information about you with the applicable Owner: (i) your first and last name, (ii) a link to your Outdoorsy Account profile page where the owner can view your Vehicle history, reviews, and description/links. All of this information will enable the Owner to decide whether to confirm or reject your booking. When an Owner confirms a booking we will share pieces of the Owner’s Identify Information, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number, the Vehicle’s address and the Owner’s email address, with the applicable Renter selected by the Owner and we will share pieces of the Renter’s Identify Information with the Owner, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number and email  
address, so that the Renter and Owner may contact one another directly. In no  
event is a Renter’s Billing Information shared with an Owner.

### Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site and Application-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, fraud detection services relating to the activity of Outdoorsy Users and improvement of the features of the Service) or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use  
it for any other purpose. We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Outdoorsy cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Outdoorsy or a third party, to protect the  
safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider  
to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.  
We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials and to our insurance services providers as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or to protect the property and rights of Outdoorsy or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information by editing the relevant part of their profile or by contacting us. If you would like us to cancel your Outdoorsy Account, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation or a legitimate business reason to retain the information contained in your Outdoorsy Account. Please note that, if you  
cancel your Outdoorsy Account, any reviews you have posted via the Services will remain publicly viewable via the Services. Please see below for privacy contact information.

### Security

Outdoorsy is very concerned with safeguarding your information. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore,  
we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Services, you can contact us.  
We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “ **personal data** ” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on the Services in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Services may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “ **clicking on** ” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Testimonials

By agreeing to the Terms of Service we may post your testimonial or reviews on the Services along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us.

### Our Policy Toward Children

The Site and Application are not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, please notify us so that we may delete such information from our files.

### Access to your account

Outdoorsy will have the right to access your account to make any changes to reservations, listings, or profile information at its sole discretion.

__legal policy privacy RV Rental __Important Documents Legal Stuff
